{
  "easyquestions": [
    {
      "question": "What is 8 - 3?",
      "answer1": "4",
      "answer2": "5",
      "correct": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 12 - 4?",
      "answer1": "8",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "8"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 7 - 2?",
      "answer1": "5",
      "answer2": "4",
      "correct": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 15 - 5?",
      "answer1": "11",
      "answer2": "10",
      "correct": "10"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 9 - 6?",
      "answer1": "3",
      "answer2": "2",
      "correct": "3"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 14 - 7?",
      "answer1": "6",
      "answer2": "7",
      "correct": "7"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 10 - 1?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "9"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 6 - 4?",
      "answer1": "1",
      "answer2": "2",
      "correct": "2"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 13 - 8?",
      "answer1": "5",
      "answer2": "6",
      "correct": "5"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is 11 - 3?",
      "answer1": "9",
      "answer2": "8",
      "correct": "8"
    }
  ]
}
